>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 我们之前说过的都是钩子，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: All we've talked about so
far are hooks, right?
如何使用挂钩状态 ?
How to do state with hooks?
它被称为无状态功能组件
It used to be called stateless
functional components and
现在人们只称其为功能组件
now people just call
them function components.
但如果你看到这些术语，那就意味着同样的事情，对吧 ?
But if you see that terminology,
those mean the same thing, right?
这就意味着一个不是一类的功能。
It just means that a function
that's not a class.
我要教你怎么做其他的类零件
I'm going to show you how to do the other
way of doing components which are class
组件。
components.
它们在一个最相似的方面发挥作用
And they function in one
most ways very similarly and
以其他方式换种方式
in other ways, a bit differently.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我们将使详细信息页面成为类组件。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So we're gonna make
the details page be a class component.
>> Brian Holt: 我接下来要做的是 :
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So what I'm gonna do here
is I'm gonna say class Details extends
React.Component， >> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
React.Component,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
>> Brian Holt: 因此，这是 JavaScript 类。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So,
this is a JavaScript class.
这事还没啥特别的对吧
There's nothing special about this yet,
right?
它扩展了 React.Component ，这意味着它有一些继承
It extends React.Component which means
that it has some inheritance that it's
能从反应成分中得到
gonna get from a react component.
>> Brian Holt: 但除了这一点，它的工作方式也相对相同。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But other than that,
it works relatively the same way.
每个类组件的一个硬需求都必须具有呈示方法。
The one hard requirement of every class
component is it must have a render method.
>> Brian Holt: 除非您具有呈示方法，否则它将不起作用。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It will not work
unless you have a render method.
>> Brian Holt: 然后，此呈示方法主要工作于函数方式
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then this render
method works mostly like how a function
组件工作，对吗 ?
component works, right?
> > 布莱恩 - 霍特( Brian Holt ) :
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
one thing to keep in mind as well is that,
>> Brian Holt: 不能使用挂钩
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You can't use hooks
有课对吧
with classes, right?
因此，使用状态仅仅只是在类组件中不起作用。
So use state will just simply not
function inside of a class component.
> > Brian Holt: 好的， >> Brian Holt: 因此，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So,
我们会在这里用每秒的渲染方法
we're gonna put in a render
method here in just a second.
>> Brian Holt: 但让我们继续输入组件 DidMount。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But let's go ahead and
put in a componentDidMount.
>> Brian Holt: 所以，组件，你可以在这里看到它会尝试
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So, component, you can see
here that it's actually gonna try and
我知道它是从 React.Component公司来的
complete it for me cuz it knows
it's coming from React.Component,
这就是它对所有这些方法的认识
that's how it knows all of these methods.
>> Brian Holt: 这些方法称为生命周期方法。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: These
are called lifecycle methods.
>> Brian Holt: 今天，我们将讨论 componentDidMount。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And, right today,
we're gonna talk about componentDidMount.
componentDidMount 是一种非常相似的使用效果，即
And componentDidMount is a very, very
similar to use effect in the sense that it
当它第一次启动时就会运行，但是它会停止。
runs when it first start up,
but then it stops.
之后就不会再跑了好吗
It doesn't run anymore after that, okay?
鉴于使用效果，您必须为其提供依赖关系以及类似的内容。
Whereas use effect, you have to give it
the dependencies and things like that.
ComponentDidMount 就像我第一次创建时就会这么做
ComponentDidMount just as like I'm gonna
do this once when I first get created and
那我就做这件事好吗
then I'm done doing this thing, okay?
这就是我们要用 componentDidMount做的事情。
So that's what we're gonna
do with componentDidMount.
>> Brian Holt: ComponentDidMount 用于执行 Ajax 请求之类的操作，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: ComponentDidMount is useful
for things like doing Ajax request,
这正是我们要做的正确的，当有人加载页面时。
which is exactly what we're gonna do,
right, when someone loads the page.
我们要去 API ，从 API 中获取宠物信息，对吧 ?
We wanna go to the API and get the pet
information back from the API, right?.
> > Brian Holt: 所以，当我们说宠物时，这正是我们要做的事情，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So, that's exactly
what we're gonna do when we say pet,
我们将从宠物主人/宠物进口的宠物进口
which we are going to import that from
import pet from frontendmasters/pet.
> > Brian Holt: 我想说的是，动物，它是一个单一的动物。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I wanna say pet.animal,
it's a single animal.
> > Brian Holt: 然后我们将通过它。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
then we're going to pass it.
我们想把我们从这里得到的身份
We want to pass that the ID
that we're getting from here,
我喜欢 /details/1 ，对吧 ?
I like it from /details/1, right?
我们想把它的号码 1 号过去
We wanna pass it this number
1 right there, right,
从 URL中获取的标识。
that ID that we're getting from the URL.
所以我们要用它的方式来解决这个问题
So the way we're gonna do
that is with this.props.id.
所以不要把它当作我们的职责
So rather than getting that in as
an argument like we were with functions it
都是我的道具
comes up this.props.
你可以保证任何从父母通过的东西
You can be assured that anything that's
passing from the parents is gonna come
从你的道具中
in from this.props.
要记住这件事道具就是它的不可改变的
The one thing to keep in mind
with this.props is its immutable,
你不能改变它
you can't change it.
所以孩子从父母那里得到道具，不能改变他们，
So, a child receives props from its
parents, and it can't change them,
只能读，对吧 ?
it can only read them, right?
它们在这个意义上是只读的。
They're read-only in that sense.
>> Brian Holt: 这是否有意义，对。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Does that make sense, yeah.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，之后，这是一个承诺。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
then after that, this is a promise.
我先说然后我们要把动物从 API中收回来
I'm gonna say .then and we're gonna
get the animal back from the API.
>> Brian Holt: 这里有一对功能。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's a pair function here.
> > Brian Holt: 我们会说 this.setState 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
we're gonna say this.setState.
>> Brian Holt: 我们将获取名为 animal.name的名称。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we're going to get
the name is going to be animal.name.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You could
put like a return here,
它就会停止给你所有的红线
it'll just stop giving
you all the red lines.
我们会在第二个方面解决这条红线的问题
We'll fix that in a second and
I'm just getting sick of the red lines.
[ LAUGH] >> Brian Holt: 名称，
[LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Name,
>> Brian Holt: Animal.name 将执行，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Animal.name will do,
动物 is， >> Brian Holt: Animal.type。
animal is,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Animal.type.
>> Brian Holt: 此处将执行将作为模板字符串的位置，因为我们有
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Here will do location which
will be a template string because we have
把几件事放在一起
to put a couple things together here.
>> Brian Holt: 我们将执行 animal.contact.address.city 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We're gonna do
animal.contact.address.city.
>> Brian Holt: Space， animal.contact.address.state。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Space,
animal.contact.address.state.
>> Brian Holt: 描述将为 animal.description。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Description
will be animal.description.
>> Brian Holt: 媒体将为动画。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
the media will be animal.photos.
>> Brian Holt: 而且品种将是 animal.breeds.primary 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
breed will be animal.breeds.primary.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 接下来我们要做的就是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then the other thing
that we're gonna do here is we're gonna
say，装入 false。
say, loading false.
> > Brian Holt: 我们会说，加载错误。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
we're gonna say, loading false.
当我们第一次加载页面时，我们会将其置于加载状态，
So, when we first load the page,
we're gonna put it in a loading state,
你正在从 API 中攫取某些东西对吧
right cuz you're grabbing
something from the API, right?
当这从 API回来的时候
And then whenever this
comes back from the API,
我们要把它装成假的
we're going to set that to loading false.
现在我们要把它装到一个装载状态
Now the way that we're gonna set it to
be a loading state is we're gonna say
就是这里的建造者
constructor up here.
>> Brian Holt: 让我们说，构造函数和构造函数将在道具中使用。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's say, constructor,
and constructor will take in the props.
你得说超级道具
And you have to say super props.
这只是某种形式的一种奇怪的仪式
This is just something kinda, it's
an odd ritual that you just have to do.
它将用属性来构造
It's going to be constructed
with properties, and
你得把这些属性处理起来，对吧 ?
you have to handle those
properties up to react, right?
这就是我的工作
So that's what this does.
超级道具说
The super props says,
hey 调用作为 React.Component的父类上的构造函数。
hey call the constructor on my parent
class which is a React.Component.
有道理吗
Is that make sense?
如果你不这样做反应会对你大喊喊叫
If you don't do this,
react will yell at you.
所以只要习惯就好了
So, just get used to doing it.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，在这里，我要设定一个初始阶段，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, here,
I'm gonna set an initial stage,
其中一些会说 : 状态 =， >> Brian Holt: 正在装入，
some would say this.state =,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Loading,
oops， >> Brian Holt: True。
oops,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: True.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，让我们谈谈 this.state 与 this.props 的关系。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let's talk about
this.state versus to this.props.
This.props 是您从父级收到的信息
This.props is information that you get
from your parent class that's handed
对你来说是吧
down to you, right?
这又是以前通过参数发生的事情。
This is, again,
what was coming in via parameters before.
现在我们又没有钩子了
Now again, we don't have hooks.
所以我们没有办法用钩子来保持有状态的事情，对吧 ?
So we don't have any way to keep
stateful things using hooks, right?
因此，我们使用类组件使用 this.state的方式。
So the way that we do that with class
components as using this.state.
this.props immutable ，仅来自父代。
Whereas this.props immutable and
only comes from the parent.
This.state 在类中是自包含的。
This.state is self-contained
within the class.
因此，任何其他组件都无法修改其状态，它是它自己的状态的主人，对吗 ?
So no other components can modify its
state, its master of its own state, right?
>> Brian Holt: 在此特定情况下，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So in this particular case,
我就像在创造第一组国家一样
I'm instantiating it like I'm
creating the first set of state but
然后我就会和你一起去
everything after that I'll do
with this.setState, right?
所以我在这里叫这个 .setState 之后，会在这里更新这个状态，对吗 ?
So after I call this .setState here, this
will update this state up here, right?
这会让我们从这些东西中得到新的状态，对吧 ?
So this will get a bunch of new
state from all this stuff, right?
然后，此装入 true将设置为装入 false。
And then this loading true,
will be set to loading false.
>> Brian Holt: 有意义吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Make sense?
好了当我打电话给这个国家的时候
Okay, so the thing to know about
when I call this .setState,
这就是所谓的肤浅的，是吧 ?
this is what's called a shallow merge,
right?
所以，我的意思是，它甚至可能只是说对象，
So, I mean,
it might even literally just says Object,
你可以忽略它只展示它的内容
you can ignore this but
just showing what it does.
对象分配， >> Brian Holt: oldState，
Object assign,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: oldState,
>> Brian Holt: newState，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: newState, right?
> > Brian Holt: 因此，这意味着如果这些碰撞中有任何碰撞，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So that basically what
that means is if any of these collide,
就像这个，这个就写这个，对吧 ?
like this one does with this one,
it will over write this one, right?
但其他一切都只是添加剂
But everything else will just be additive.
所以如果有其他事情， >> Brian Holt: 这个
So if this had some other thing,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This
不会被覆盖，这之后还会存在，对吧 ?
would not be overwritten,
this would still exist afterwards, right?
但很肤浅对吧
But it is shallow, right?
所以如果我有深度的嵌套对象，就不会被覆盖了，对，所以
So if I have deeply nested objects,
those won't get overwritten, right, so
它才是最顶层的
it just does the top level.
>> Brian Holt: 这就是如何使用类组件的状态。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And that's how you
do state with class components.
这就是我一直在做状态，直到钩子出现的时候。
This is how I've been doing state for
a really long time until hooks came along.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Something
else I wanna call out here,
请注意此处的箭头函数，而不是此处的函数。
notice these an arrow function here
instead of saying function here.
>> Brian Holt: 你可能注意到我使用了很多的箭头函数
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You’ve probably noticed
that I use a lot of arrow functions just
根据我编码的性质在这个地方它实际上是必需的
by the nature of how I code, this in
this place, it's actually required.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 我不想说
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I don't wanna say required,
如果你不这样做就很难了
it's very difficult if
you don't do it this way.
>> Brian Holt: 为什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So why?
为什么会有这个问题呢 ?
Why is this a problem here?
如果我把功能放在这里是什么
Well, if I put a function here,
what is this?
>> Brian Holt: 答案不是你想要的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: The answer is not
what you would want it to be.
我不知道这会是什么但
[LAUGH] I don't actually
know it's gonna be, but
这不可能是你想要的对吧
it's not gonna be what
you'd want it to be, right?
当我在此处放置函数时，它会在调用此函数时创建新的上下文。
When I put function here, it creates
a new context when this is invoked.
This.then 将在其他地方调用。
This.then is going to be
invoked somewhere else.
这可能是 " 窗口 " ，可能是承诺本身。
That might be Window,
it might be the promise itself.
我不知道它是怎么被调用的
I'm not actually sure
what it gets invoked on.
但是，如果我执行一个箭头函数，将会得到这个结果。
But, if I do an arrow function
instead this will get.
它不会创建一个新的上下文，即箭头的功能，
It will not create a new context,
which is what arrow functions do,
他们不会创造新的环境对吧
they don't create new contexts, right?
这将是正确的。
So this will be correct.
>> Brian Holt: 这是否有意义 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Does that make sense?
>> Brian Holt: 一些经典要素，这是非常重要的，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Some of classic components,
what this is very important, right?
这其实是他们选择挂钩方向的原因之一
It's actually one of the reasons why they
chose to go the directions of hooks is
因为这很难教，对吧 ?
because this is kind of hard to teach,
right?
>> Brian Holt: 可以。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It can be.
>> Brian Holt: 就像你需要知道的几件事一样。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There's just like a handful
of things that you need to be aware of.
我想，在这之后，它很可能已经过去了。
And I think after that it's
pretty to move past what this is.
>> Brian Holt: 并且，您也可以放入 then，您可以放入 console.error。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And, you can also put here
in the then, you can put console.error.
因此，如果 API 中存在任何错误，那么它将仅将其记录到控制台。
So if there's any errors in the API, so
it will just log it out to the console.
>> Brian Holt: 您应该具有更好的错误处理方式，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You should have better
error handling than this, right?
您应该将其报告给您的服务，并且
You should report it to your service and
显示您的错误是一些有用的错误消息。
show that your error are some
useful error message.
这不是错误处理的过程。
This is not a course on error handling.
他们有这方面的课程你应该小心点
They have a course on that,
you should watch that.
[ 笑声]
[LAUGH]